(UPBEAT LILTING MUSIC)
- THIS AIN'T NO DISCO
IT AIN'T NO COUNTRY
CLUB, EITHER.
THIS IS L.A.
♪ ALL I WANNA DO IS HAVE A
LITTLE FUN BEFORE I DIE ♪
♪ SAYS THE MAN NEXT
TO ME OUT OF NOWHERE ♪
♪ IT'S APROPOS OF NOTHING,
HE SAYS HIS NAME IS WILLIAM ♪
♪ BUT I'M SURE HE'S BILL
OR BILLY OR MAC OR BUDDY ♪
♪ AND HE'S PLAIN UGLY TO ME ♪
♪ AND I WONDER IF HE'S
EVER HAD A DAY OF FUN ♪
♪ IN HIS WHOLE LIFE ♪
♪ NOW WE ARE DRINKING
BEER AT NOON ON TUESDAY ♪
♪ IN A BAR THAT FACES
A GIANT CAR WASH ♪
♪ THE GOOD PEOPLE OF THE WORLD ♪
♪ ARE WASHING THEIR CARS
ON THEIR LUNCH BREAK ♪
♪ HOSING AND SCRUBBING AS BEST
THEY CAN IN SKIRTS AND SUITS ♪
♪ THEY DRIVE THEIR SHINY
DATSUNS AND BUICKS ♪
♪ BACK TO THE PHONE COMPANY,
AND THE RECORD STORE TOO ♪
♪ WELL, THEY'RE NOTHING
LIKE BILLY AND ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE ALL I WANNA
DO IS HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ I GOT A FEELING I'M
NOT THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA DO
IS HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ I GOT A FEELING I'M
NOT THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA DO
IS HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ UNTIL THE SUN COMES UP ♪
♪ OVER SANTA MONICA BOULEVARD ♪
(UPBEAT LILTING MUSIC CONTINUES)
♪ I LIKE A GOOD BEER BUZZ
EARLY IN THE MORNING ♪
♪ AND BILLY LIKES TO PEEL THE
LABELS FROM HIS BOTTLES OF BUD ♪
♪ HE SHREDS THEM ON THE BAR,
THEN HE LIGHTS EVERY MATCH ♪
♪ IN AN OVERSIZED PACK,
LETTING EACH ONE BURN ♪
♪ DOWN TO HIS THICK FINGERS ♪
♪ BEFORE BLOWING AND
CURSING THEM OUT ♪
♪ AND HE'S WATCHING
THE BOTTLES OF BUD ♪
♪ AS THEY SPIN ON THE FLOOR ♪
♪ AND A HAPPY COUPLE
ENTERS THE BAR ♪
♪ DANGEROUSLY CLOSE
TO ONE ANOTHER ♪
♪ THE BARTENDER LOOKS
UP FROM HIS WANT ADS ♪
♪ BUT ALL I WANNA DO
IS HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ I GOT A FEELING I'M
NOT THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA DO
IS HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ I GOT A FEELING I'M
NOT THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA DO
IS HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ UNTIL THE SUN COMES UP ♪
♪ OVER SANTA MONICA BOULEVARD ♪
(UPBEAT LILTING MUSIC CONTINUES)
♪ OTHERWISE THE BAR IS OURS ♪
♪ THE DAY AND THE NIGHT
AND THE CAR WASH, TOO ♪
♪ THE MATCHES, AND THE BUDS,
AND THE CLEAN AND DIRTY CARS ♪
♪ THE SUN AND THE MOON ♪
♪ BUT ALL I WANNA DO
IS HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ I GOT A FEELING I'M
NOT THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA DO
IS HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ I GOT A FEELING THE
PARTY HAS JUST BEGUN ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA DO
IS HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ I WON'T TELL YOU THAT
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA DO
IS HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ UNTIL THE SUN COMES UP ♪
♪ OVER SANTA MONICA BOULEVARD ♪
(UPBEAT LILTING MUSIC SWELLS)